Guide to the Skagit County Oral History Project records 1962-1979
Western Washington University, Center for Pacific Northwest Studies
- Marie Jurkovich (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, March 17, 1978; RIII-173 (Reel 4)
  Format: Transcript (29 pages), Cassette (1 hour 30 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Working in the canneries of Anacortes, Recipe for preserving sardines, Life in Yugoslavia
- Marion and Worth B. Knapp (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, March 16, 1978; RIII-174 (Reel 4)
  Format: Transcript (53 pages), Cassette (1 hour 45 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Early Anacortes and Guemes, Knapp's Machine Shop, First Ford dealership, the Chinese in Anacortes
- Levina Johnson (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, March 20, 1978; RIII-175
  Format: Reel-to-reel (1 hour)
  Notes: no transcript
- Rodney E. Gray (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger and Barbara Heacock, March 22, 1978; RIII-176 (Reel 4)
  Subjects: Truck logging, Blanchard Mill, Darius Kinsey, Mack versus other trucks. He has been hauling for 74 years and is still going at 90 years of age.
- Marcy Chemalis (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, March 23, 1978; RIII-177
  Format: Reel-to-reel (1 hour 30 min)
  Subjects: Concrete, Mining, Marble Creek, Marblemount, Rocky Creek, Married and came to Skagit County in 1919, Big Lake, Logging, Indians, Prohibition, Bootlegging, Card rooms, Midwives
  Notes: no transcript, only an outline
- Bess Conn Fields Rogers and Mark Gilkey (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Elva Mary Giard, June 20, 1978; RIII-178 (Reel 4)
  Format: Transcript (38 pages), Cassette (1 hour), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Early Edison area, Gilkey towing, Family remembrances - the Gilkeys and the Conns are related
- Maurice Splane (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, March 28, 1978; RIII-179, a, b (Reel 4)
  Format: Transcript (62 pages), Cassette (2 hours), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Sedro-Woolley Iron Works, Machine shops, Working on logging locomotives, Upper Skagit River Game Department, Blacksmithing in logging camps
- Charles and Nellie Marquart (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, March 28, 1978; RIII-180 (Reel 4)
  Format: Transcript (12 pages), Cassette (30 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Equality Colony, Early Edison and Blanchard area, Blanchard Mill, Shingle weaver, Accidents, Attended school at the Colony
- Will C. Fisher (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, March 29, 1978; RIII-181 (Reel 4)
  Format: Transcript (52 pages), Cassette (1 hour 30 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Hook tender for the English Logging Company and other logging companies, IWW, Dairy farming, Drainage, Steelheading, Cider making, Moonshining
- Ellis and Lillian Andrews (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, March 30, 1978; RIII-182 (Reel 4)
  Format: Transcript (52 pages), Cassette (1 hour 45 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: 1916 snow, Summit Park, Grandfather was an early Cypress Island settler
- Will F. Fisher (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, March 30, 1978; RIII-183
  Subjects: Immigration west from Kansas, Threshing machinery, Horses, Thoroughbred racing
- Henry Tjersland (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, March 31, 1978; RIII-184 (Reel 4)
  Format: Transcript (41 pages), Cassette (2 hours), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Steamboats, Threshing, Clearing land, Diking, Flailing cabbage, Horses, Chinese, Evergreen Hotel at Conway, Prison Rock Quarry
- Dollie Gilkey (Mrs. Dave) (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, March 31, 1978; RIII-185 (Reel 4)
  Format: Transcript (14 pages), Reel-to-reel (45 min)
  Subjects: Born during the flood of 1894, Gilkey Towboat Company, the Interurban
- Eben Bennett (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, March 31, 1978; RIII-186 (Reel 4)
  Format: Transcript (50 pages), Cassette (1 hour 40 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Threshing, Dairy farming, the San Francisco Earthquake was felt on the Skagit River ice
- Dorothy A. Stewart (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, April 4, 1978; RIII-187 (Reel 4)
  Format: Transcript (24 pages), Cassette(40 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Floods of 1909, 1916, 1921, Predicting floods by the weather, Early Riverside, Witnessed the 1903 Trainwreck.
- Ora and Alice Higgs (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, April 5, 1978; RIII-188 (Reel 4)
  Subjects: West to Edison in 1937, Threshing, Horses, Breeding saddle horses, Shingle bolt speeder car, Worked with Reuben R. Boyd
- Maynard C. Collier (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, April 5, 1978; RIII-189 (Reel 4)
  Format: Transcript (34 pages), Reel-to-reel (1 hour 40 min)
  Subjects: West from Minnesota with the Trafton family, Early Anacortes, Pile driver for the Fidalgo Island Packing Company, Mill accidents, Farming, Dairying
- Ralph McKibben (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, April 6, 1978; RIII-190 (Reel 4)
  Format: Transcript (18 pages), Reel-to-reel (40 min)
  Subjects: Threshing, Horses: Trotters, Pacers, and Standardbreds
- John Ball (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Peter Hefflefinger, April 6, 1978; RIII-191 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (30 pages), Reel-to-reel (1 hour 20 min)
  Subjects: Ball family in Skagit County, Bayview Ridge, Fredonia, Burlington Iron Works
- George Peth (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Elva Mary Giard, June 26, 1979; RIII-192 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (45 pages), Cassette (1 hour 30 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Informative discussion of Skagit Valley in the early days, Father was John Peth, Sr., Peth acquisition of land through financing others
- Nina B. Hurley (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Elva Mary Giard, June 27, 1979; RIII-193 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (34 pages), Cassette (1 hour), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: LaConner, Sedro-Woolley, Taught by Mary Purcell
- James Pedley Kean (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Elva Mary Giard, July 12, 1979; RIII-194 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (37 pages), Cassette (1 hour), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Mt. Vernon, Early businesses, Schools, Skagit River
- Milton Morrison (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Donna Holt, March 1, 1976; RIII-195 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (3 pages), Cassette (10 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Depression, WWII
  Restrictions: none - Easton Project Donation
- Roy Miller (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Kathie Naier, January 1, 1974; RIII-196 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (14 pages), Cassette (30 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Transportation, Farming, Entertainment, Circus, Decaptra, Kerosene lamps, Childhood, Silk, WWI, Environmental issues, Early theater, Radio, Dancing, Baseball, Streetcars
- Richie Arlene King (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Kristi King, January 22, 1976; RIII-197 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (3 pages), Cassette (5 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Schools, Alger, Bow, Marjorie Dorsey
- Dee and James Snowden (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Kelly Snowden, October 15, 1975; RIII-198 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (15 pages), Cassette (30 min)
  Subjects: LaConner, Farming, University, Mt. Baker climb, Family history, School, Dances, Avon
- Bea Gardner (Mrs. Herb) (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Gretchen Caldwell, January 1, 1975; RIII-199 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (3 pages), Cassette (5 min)
  Subjects: Entertainment, University of Washington
- Joseph Leland Parker (Year of Birth: 1905) interviewed by: John Hughes, May 28, 1905; RIII-200 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (9 pages), Cassette (15 min)
  Subjects: Mt. Vernon, Family history, Cattle business, Grocery stores, Indians, Depression, Fires, Sports, Recreation, School, Maritime
- Carroll Anderson (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Teresa Eschbach and Susan Moore, May 1, 1975; RIII-201 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (9 pages), Cassette (1 hour)
  Subjects: LaConner history, Dikes, Floods, School, Gaches family and mansion
- Victor Bushart (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Bob Junquist, spring 1974; RIII-202 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (6 pages), Cassette (15 min)
  Subjects: Entertainment in early days, Depression, Schools, Stores
- Virginia Moen (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Jeanne Cushman, April 2, 1974; RIII-203 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (4 pages), Cassette (5 min)
  Subjects: March's Point, Pleasant Ridge, Fir Island, Rexville, Schools, Lutherans
- Mrs. Ed Poppe (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Kathy Stowell, March 17, 1976; RIII-204 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (5 pages), Cassette (10 min)
  Subjects: Schools, Avon
- Frank McCormick (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Brian Hager, May 27, 1905; RIII-205, 206 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (17 pages), Cassette (45 min)
  Subjects: Farming, Mt. Vernon, Telegraphy job, Mining
  Notes: one transcript
- Mabel Roseland Gansberg (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Jeff Cobb and Dave Elliot, November 1, 1974; RIII-207 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (10 pages), Cassette (30 min)
  Subjects: Teaching, Depression, War, Entertainment
- Margaret Maupin (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Julie Stewart, May 28, 1905; RIII-208 (Reel 5)
  Subjects: Mt. Vernon, Farming, Skagit River freezing, Flood
- Thomas Crumrine (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Randy Crumrine, June 10, 1975; RIII-209 (Reel 5)
  Subjects: 1930s
- William Burger (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Carl Coley, May 27, 1905; RIII-210 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (11 pages), Cassette (30 min)
  Subjects: Roads, Schools, Depression, Logging
- Clara Soler (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Chris Soler, June 4, 1974; RIII-211 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (14 pages), Cassette (30 min)
  Subjects: Stanwood, Farming, Diking, Hobos, Automobile accidents, Scandinavians
- Carl Johnson (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Scott Allquist, January 20, 1975; RIII-212 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (6 pages), Cassette (15 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Housing, Schools, Grocery store
- Kathleen Eruine Sharp (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Betsy Henshaw, November 9, 1973; RIII-213 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (8 pages), Cassette (25 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Anacortes, Schools, Mr. Sharpe as county commissioner
- Jack [Bill?] and Darlene Pickler (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Unknown, March 26, 1976; RIII-214 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (8 pages), Cassette (30 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: School, Flood, Mt. Vernon
- Jack Sicklesteel (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Unknown, March 26, 1976; RIII-215 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (9 pages), Cassette (30 min)
  Subjects: Mt. Vernon, WWII, Towing job
- Jack Wollan (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Terry Faber, October 28, 1975; RIII-216 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (13 pages), Cassette (30 min)
  Subjects: Conway, Depression, Schools, Flood, Sternwheelers, Logging, Hunting fowl
- Jack Benston (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Brian Hatcher, Steve Mackey, Ryan Johnson, May 26, 1905; RIII-217 (Reel 5)
  Subjects: Burlington, Sedro-Woolley, Streetcars, Interurban, Floods, Darigold, Fires, Logging, Hunting, Canneries
- Karl Lindall (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Unknown, October 1, 1973; RIII-218 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (4 pages), Cassette (25 min)
  Subjects: Typhoid fever epidemic, Mining, Farming
- William C. Moore (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Steve Schroder, Undated; RIII-219 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (38 pages), Cassette (2 hours)
  Subjects: Baker Lake area, Prospecting, Mountaineering, Joe Morovit
- Susan and Brice Franklin (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: interviewee's daughter, Undated; RIII-220 (Reel 5)
  Subjects: Schools, Baking, Movie made in Mt. Vernon, Sternwheelers, Flood, Logging, Smallpox epidemic
- Anne Ferwerda Richards (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Deryl Walls, Undated; RIII-221 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (33 pages), Cassette (time not listed)
  Subjects: Work as seamstress, clothing designer, painter, dollmaker, owned clothing store/gallery in Mt. Vernon
- Alice Walker Hanson (Year of Birth: 1910) interviewed by: Deryl Walls, November 19, 1979; RIII-222 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (13 pages), Cassette (time not listed), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Indians, Gypsies, Bayview, Prohibition, illegal alcohol, electricity, Depression, Childbirth, Floods, Entertainment
- Harry Johnson (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Deryl Walls, November 27, 1979; RIII-223 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (27 pages), Cassette(1 hour 15 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Farming, Floods, Diking, Kidnapping, Prohibition, Logging, Roads, Medicine, Schools, Early Days
- John Peth (Year of Birth: 1901) interviewed by: Deryl Walls and Dave Van Meer, December 3, 1979; RIII-224, 1-2 a, b (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (87 pages), Cassette (4 hours), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Moonshine, Indian burial grounds, Sullivan Grove, Edison, Farming - dairy, beef, pig, seed, potato, sheep, horse, Depression, Founded Skagit State Bank, Early Days, County Burials, Cooking, LaConner, Conway, Olympia Marsh, Life in Texas, Childhood stories, Blacksmithing, Equality Colony, Floods, Diking, Logging, Mules, Anacortes, WWII, Indian canoes, Lumber business, Rodeos
  Notes: four tapes and three transcripts
- Mervin and Joy Benham (Year of Birth: 1902) interviewed by: Deryl Walls, December 7, 1979; RIII-225 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (31 pages), Cassette (1 hour), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Newspaper publishing, Logging and lumber mills, Floods and dikes, Schools, Settlement of Walker Valley (South Clear Lake), Interurban Railroad, Depression, Farming, Community Entertainment, 4H Clubs, Indians, Home remedies, President Taft
- Milo Moore (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Deryl Walls, Karen Dalan, February 6, 1980; RIII-226, a, b (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (61 pages), Cassette (2 hours), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: LaConner politics, Fire department, Fishing, Fisheries Department - local, state, federal, Marshall Plan, Greek, Korean,and Japanese fisheries, Korean War, WPA, Prohibition, Dikes, Depression, Courthouse, Hatcheries, Indian fishing treaties, Nuclear power, Mining, Fish traps, River ferries
- Paul Wells (Year of Birth: 1904) interviewed by: Deryl Walls, February 8, 1980; RIII-227 (Reel 5)
  Subjects: LaConner, Mt. Vernon, Pharmacist, Drugs, Medicines, Home remedies, Prohibition, Depression, Floods, Crime, WWI, Circuses, Schools, Transportation, Dikes, Telephones, Ann and Dr. Richards
- Bill and Edith (Welts) Moore (Year of Birth: 1902) interviewed by: Deryl Walls, February 11, 1980; RIII-228 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (19 pages), Cassette (1 hour 30 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: LaConner, State Constitution, Mt. Vernon, Entertainment, Daily life, President Taft, Indians, Ethnic groups, Darius Kinsey, Churches, Skagit River - jams, floods, Depression, Seattle, Electricity, Kidnapping
- William Alvord (Year of Birth: 1904) interviewed by: Deryl Walls, Karen Dalan, February 14, 1980; RIII-229, a, b (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (52 pages), Cassette (1 hour 35 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Family history, Floods, Schools, Prohibition, Indians, Fishing, Depression, LaConner, Fish Pirates, WWI, Influenza epidemic, Ethnic settlements, Police work, Medical care, Home remedies, Homesteading, Dairy farming, Childhood, Floods, Refrigeration, Logging camps
- Roberta Moore Nelson (Year of Birth: after 1918) interviewed by: Deryl Walls, Karen Dalan, February 22, 1980; RIII-230 (Reel 5)
  Subjects: Family history, Fishing and fish traps, Farming, Bridges, Medical care, Civic life, Local Politics, Liquor control, Tulip show, Naval air base, Fidalgo allied arts, LaConner, WWII, Swinomish Indians, basket weaving, canoe racing
- Dorothy Gibbons Siegfried (Year of Birth: 1904) interviewed by: Deryl Walls, Karen Dalan, March 6, 1980; RIII-231 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (15 pages), Cassette (1 hour 15 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: LaConner, Local businesses, Clubs, Civic life, Bridges, Telephone, Indians, Prohibition, Family history, Home remedies, Winters
- Josephine Hanaford Spratley (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Deryl Walls, March 19, 1980; RIII-232 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (20 pages), Cassette (1 hour), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Move west from Kansas, Family history, Daily life, Chataquas, Cars, Lumber camp, Pow-wows, Schools, Medical care, Influenza epidemic, University of Washington, Local businesses, Chinese, Depression, Floods, Swinomish Indians, Mt. Vernon, Snowstorms, Interurban
- Minnie Gallacher Waugh (Year of Birth: 1877) interviewed by: Deryl Walls, March 26, 1980; RIII-233 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (23 pages), Cassette (1 hour 30 min), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Telephone, Schools, Swinomish Indians, Farming, Depression, LaConner, Family history, Entertainment, Daily life, Smallpox epidemic, Floods, Hops
- Viola Dolittle Cameron (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Deryl Walls, March 28, 1980; RIII-234 (Reel 5)
  Subjects: Murder, Schools, Indians, Wars, Prohibition, Floods, Dikes, Epidemics, Pest house, Clubs, Move west from Kansas, Mt. Vernon, Local businesses, President Taft, William Jennings Bryan, Pioneering, Local politics, Depression, Interurban, Postal service, Churches, Cars
- Louis E. Humphrey (Year of Birth: 1911) interviewed by: Dana Dhams, Bill McGuinness, Karen Dalan, May 1, 1980; RIII-235, a, b (Reel 5)
  Subjects: Burlington, Family history, Homesteading, Mt. Vernon, LaConner, Swinomish Indians, Pioneer Picnic, Immigration from Sweden, Electricity, Local businesses, Cars, Church meetings, Circus Days, Milk cooperatives, Transportation, Interurban, Burlington family names, High school teacher names
- Ralph W. Nelson (Year of Birth: 1906) interviewed by: Dana Dhams, Karen Dalan, May 15, 1980; RIII-236 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (44 pages), Cassette (time not listed), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Immigration from Norwaty, LaConner local businesses and buildings and municipal issues, Floods and dikes, Snowstorms, Schools, Farming, Politics, Transportation, Fish traps and gillnetting, Indians, Scandinavian population, Boeing's first airplane, Electricity, Entertainment, Depression, Fraternal orders, Unions, WWII, Canneries, Fires, Prohibition, Food
- Lila Wallace Auckland (Year of Birth: 1912) interviewed by: Dana Dhams, May 20, 1980; RIII-237 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (33 pages), Cassette (time not listed), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Family history, Immigration west, Schools, LaConner buildings and businesses, Indians, Entertainment, Clubs, Childhood, Smoking, Trains
- Hubert E. Crosby (Year of Birth: 1902) interviewed by: Dana Russo, June 26, 1980; RIII-238 (Reel 5)
  Subjects: Early theatre in Anacortes, Mt. Vernon, Seattle
- James P. Kean (Year of Birth: 1904) interviewed by: Dana Russo, July 14, 1980; RIII-239 (Reel 5)
  Subjects: Mt. Vernon, Barbershop, Childhood, Milk companies, Floods and dikes, Money, School, Entertainment, Fires, WWII, Depression, Equality Colony, Trains, Logging, Snowstorm
- Alger A. Moberg (Year of Birth: 1888) interviewed by: Dana Russo, August 8, 1980; RIII-240 (Reel 5)
  Subjects: Immigration from Minnesota, Early Mt. Vernon, Local businesses, Early movies, Bridges, Alger, Water supply, Dikes and floods, Schools, Entertainment
- Louis Humphrey (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Dana Russo, August 5, 1980; RIII-241 (Reel 5)
  Subjects: Early theatre, Musical accompaniment, Transportation, Film exchanges, Stage shows, Vaudeville, Radio
- Walter Blade (Year of Birth: 1880) interviewed by: Dana Russo, August 26, 1980; RIII-242 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (9 pages), Cassette (time not listed), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Family history, Immigration from Scandinavia, Blacksmith shop, Car dealership, Early LaConner, Local businesses, Keystone Theatre, Schools, Newspaper
- Alger A. Moberg (Year of Birth: 1888) interviewed by: Dana Russo, August 27, 1980; RIII-243 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (8 pages), Cassette (time not listed), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Mt. Vernon local businesses, Seattle student life, Alaska-Yukon Exhibit, Camping at Rosario, Trains, Floods, Coal, Entertainment, Snowstorms
- John Tursi (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: Keith Wiemerslage, David Van Meer, Undated; RIII-244 (Reel 5)
  Format: Transcript (19 pages), Cassette (time not listed), Reel-to-reel
  Subjects: Depression, Civilian Conservation Corps, Meals, Accommodations, Daily routine, Deception Pass, Komo Kulshan Ranger Station, Fire fighting, Snowstorms, Anacortes
- Genevieve Ball (Year of Birth: unknown) interviewed by: unknown, Undated; RIII-245
  Format: Cassette (time not listed)
- Al and Martha Covert (Year of Birth:: unknown) interviewed by: Barbara Heacock, Undated; RIII-246 (Reel 5)
  Subjects: Weyerhauser lumber mills, Strikes, Mill management, Lumber grading
  Notes: Cassette and reel-to-reel probably available under RIII-42. See catalog card
- Edison History (Year of Birth:: unknown) interviewed by: unknown, Undated; RIII-247
  Notes: By Irene Schumaker and Friends, Feb. 19, 1991 for Oral History Section